// let questions = [
//     {
//         numb: 1,
//         question: "What does HTML stands for?",
//         answer: "HyperText Markup Language",
//         options: [
//             "A. HighText Machine Language",
//             "B. HyperText and links Markup Language",
//             "C. HyperText Markup Language",
//             "D. None of these"
//         ]
//     },

//     {
//         numb: 2,
//         question: "What does CSS stands for?",
//         answer: "Cascading Style Sheet",
//         options: [
//             "A. Cute Style Sheet",
//             "B. Cascading Style Sheet",
//             "C. Computer Style Size",
//             "D. Computation Style Sheet"

//         ]
//     },

//     {
//         numb: 3,
//         question: "<br/> What type of tag is this?",
//         answer: "Break Tag",
//         options: [
//             "A. Break Tag",
//             "B. A broken one",
//             "C. An opening Tag",
//             "D. All of these"
//            ]
//     },

//     {
//         numb: 4,
//         question: "What is SQL stands for ?",
//         answer: "Structured Query Language",
//         options: [
//             "A. Semi-Structured Query Lang",
//             "B. Structured Query Language",
//             "C. Both A. and B.",
//             "D. Only B"
//         ]
//     },

//     {
//         numb: 5,
//         question: "What is PHP stands for?",
//         answer: "Hypertext Preprocessor",
//         options: [
//             "A. Pre-processor Hyper Plane",
//             "B. Plane Hyper Plane",
//             "C. Hypertext Preprocessor",
//             "D. None of these above"

//         ]
//     },
// ];

let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What does HTML stands for?",
        answer: "C. HyperText Markup Language",
        options: [
            "A. HighText Machine Language",
            "B. HyperText and links Markup Language",
            "C. HyperText Markup Language",
            "D. None of these"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What does CSS stands for?",
        answer: "B. Cascading Style Sheet",
        options: [
            "A. Cute Style Sheet",
            "B. Cascading Style Sheet",
            "C. Computer Style Size",
            "D. Computation Style Sheet"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "<br/> What type of tag is this?",
        answer: "A. Break Tag",
        options: [
            "A. Break Tag",
            "B. A broken one",
            "C. An opening Tag",
            "D. All of these"
           ]
    },

    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is SQL stands for ?",
        answer: "B. Structured Query Language",
        options: [
            "A. Semi-Structured Query Lang",
            "B. Structured Query Language",
            "C. Both A. and B.",
            "D. Only B"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is PHP stands for?",
        answer: "C. Hypertext Preprocessor",
        options: [
            "A. Pre-processor Hyper Plane",
            "B. Plane Hyper Plane",
            "C. Hypertext Preprocessor",
            "D. None of these above"

        ]
    },
];

